(Howard:)Put her away,
'cause I don't have a third one.
Yes!
(whoops)
(Amy:)Rajesh eight, Penny four.
(Leonard:)Sorry,
he's really good.
(Bernadette:)Hey, Raj.
(Bernadette:)if Howard can't
keep the TARDIS,
(Bernadette:)how great would it
look at your place?
(Leonard:)What?
(Howard:)Yeah, what?
(Bernadette:)I don't know much
about Doctor Who,
(Bernadette:)but if, um, you were to put this
(Bernadette:)right outside your front door
and open up the back,
(Bernadette:)it would be like
your entire apartment was
(Bernadette:)the inside of the TARDIS,
(Bernadette:)which is pretty cool
(Bernadette:)'cause on the show,
the inside of the TARDIS
(Bernadette:)is bigger than the outside.
(Bernadette:)But then again, I don't know
much about Doctor Who.
(Howard:)Don't listen to her.
(Howard:)You and I go way back--
we're like brothers.
(Raj:)We are. We are.
(clears throat)
Oh, no!
What a terrible serve!
(Raj:)Sorry, brother.
(Amy:)Eight-five.
This is ridiculous.
(Howard:)I want a new champion.